Robert Vazquez

Experienced Computer Programmer in various Coding languages, Web Development, Computer Hardware & Software, and Database Administration who is motivated to start a career in my line of work and skills. I also work great with others and clients, always allowing room for new learning opportunities and improvement.

1870 Waltrip Ct. Yuba City, CA 95991 **530-305-8576** robert55vazquez@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

J.A Sutherland Inc, Chico, (530) 529-1470 — Taco Bell Food Champion

June 2015 - July 2016

Handled cashier, food distribution, food preparing, and customer service.

K3, Yuba City — Web Designer

June 2019 - September 2019

Collaborated on creating k3scoop.com hired to design, develop,

and create k3sportfitness.com solely for the company.

K3, Yuba City — IT Technician

September 2019 - August 2020

Personal IT Tech handling companies website updates

and maintaining computer software and hardware.

EDUCATION

Live Oak High School, Live Oak — High School Diploma

August 2010 - June 2014

Butte College, Oroville — Computer Programming — Associates in Science Degree

Spring 2018 - Fall 2020 Will Receive Degree/Walk Spring 2021

PROJECTS

Butte College Web Scraper — *Project Manager*

Fall 2020

I was in charge of database, documentation, software, and testing leads to create a web server that scrapes the Butte College Career Programs using Javascript, Node Js, Cheerio, HTML, CSS, and MySQL Database.

SKILLS

- Microsoft OS
 - XP ,Vista, 7,8, 10
 - Office
 - Excel
 - Word
 - o Outlook
 - Powerpoint
 - Visual Studio
 Code
- Mac OSX
 - Snow Leopard
 - Current
 - Xcode
- Linux Essentials
 - CentOS
- Advanced Computer Software and Hardware Skills
- Network and Security Administration and Repair
- Computer
 Troubleshooting and
 Repair
- Programming and Algorithms
- Database Designs
- Web Development
- Bash, Command Prompt, and zsh commands

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- C++
- HTML/CSS/Jquery
- Java/Script
- Python
- MySQL